<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<type name="Forms" fullname="Helpers.Forms" category="Helpers" gametitle="">
  <summary>
            Provides methods that can be used to look up and retrieve any available forms.
            </summary>
  <method name="Find" extension="false">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Form" /> Find(<c>uint</c>)</signature>
    <summary>
            Retrieves the form which has the specified Form ID, in the main plugin, or returns <c>null</c> if no such form could be found.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="Find" extension="false">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Form" /> Find(<c>string</c>)</signature>
    <summary>
            Retrieves the form which has the specified Editor ID, or returns <c>null</c> if no such form could be found. 
            If more forms share the specified Editor ID, the form loaded or created last will be retrieved.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="Find" extension="false">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Form" /> Find(<c>string</c>,<c>uint</c>)</signature>
    <summary>
            Retrieves the form which has the specified Form ID and belongs to the specified plugin, or returns <c>null</c> if no such form could be found.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="FindAll" extension="false">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.FormCollection" /> FindAll()</signature>
    <summary>
            Retrieves all forms that are currently available.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="FindAllHavingTag" extension="false">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.FormCollection" /> FindAllHavingTag(<c>string</c>)</signature>
    <summary>
            Retrieves all forms that have been tagged with the specified text. If no forms have been tagged with the specified text the returned collection will be empty.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <remarks>
    <p>
            Method <code>Forms.FindAll()</code> will retrieve a huge number of forms and on its own is not very practical 
            and iterating such a huge list is not very effective. This method is used as a starting point in a chain of filtering methods 
            that are used to retrieve a more specific set of forms instead.
            </p>
    <p>
            While any form can be retrieved through the <code>Forms</code> helper, keep in mind they cannot be modified. 
            They can only be tagged or assigned as a reference or its parts copied to the properties of the <code>Target</code> form.
            </p>
  </remarks>
</type>