<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<type name="Form" fullname="Forms.Form" category="Forms" gametitle="">
  <summary>
            Represents a form the type of which is either unknown, unsupported or unresolved.
            To convert an unknown form to a specific form use the appropriate extension method.
            Properties and methods provided by this class are available to all forms.
            </summary>
  <property name="EditorId" gametitle="">
    <signature>
      <c>string</c> EditorId</signature>
    <summary>
            Gets or sets the Editor ID associated with this form.
            </summary>
  </property>
  <property name="FormId" gametitle="">
    <signature>
      <c>uint</c> FormId</signature>
    <summary>
            Gets the Form ID associated with this form.
            </summary>
  </property>
  <method name="HasTag" extension="false" gametitle="">
    <signature>
      <c>bool</c> HasTag(<c>string</c>)</signature>
    <summary>
            Determines whether this form has been tagged with the specified text.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="Tag" extension="false" gametitle="">
    <signature>
      <c>void</c> Tag(<c>string</c>)</signature>
    <summary>
            Tags this form with the specified text.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsAlch" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Alch" /> AsAlch()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Potion</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not a <b>Potion</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsAmmo" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Ammo" /> AsAmmo()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to an <b>Ammo</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not an <b>Ammo</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsArmo" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Armo" /> AsArmo()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to an <b>Armor</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not an <b>Armor</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsCobj" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Cobj" /> AsCobj()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Constructible Object</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not a <b>Constructible Object</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsColl" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Coll" /> AsColl()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Collision Layer</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not a <b>Collision Layer</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsEnch" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Ench" /> AsEnch()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to an <b>Enchantment</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not an <b>Enchantment</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsEqup" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Equp" /> AsEqup()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to an <b>Equipment Type</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not an <b>Equipment Type</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsExpl" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Expl" /> AsExpl()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to an <b>Explosion</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not an <b>Explosion</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsFlst" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Flst" /> AsFlst()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Form List</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not a <b>Form List</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsGlob" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Glob" /> AsGlob()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Global Variable</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not a <b>Global Variable</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsGmst" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Gmst" /> AsGmst()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Game Setting</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not a <b>Game Setting</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsImgs" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Imgs" /> AsImgs()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Image Space</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not an <b>Image Space</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsIpds" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Ipds" /> AsIpds()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Impact Data Set</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not an <b>Impact Data Set</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsKywd" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Kywd" /> AsKywd()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Keyword</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not a <b>Keyword</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsLigh" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Ligh" /> AsLigh()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Light</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not a <b>Light</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsMatt" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Matt" /> AsMatt()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Material</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not a <b>Material</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsMgef" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Mgef" /> AsMgef()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Magic Effect</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not a <b>Magic Effect</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsProj" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Proj" /> AsProj()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Projectile</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not a <b>Projectile</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsRace" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Race" /> AsRace()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Race</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not a <b>Race</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsRfct" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Rfct" /> AsRfct()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Visual Effect</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not a <b>Visual Effect</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsSndr" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Sndr" /> AsSndr()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Sound</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not a <b>Sound</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsSpel" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Spel" /> AsSpel()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Spell</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not a <b>Spell</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsSpgd" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Spgd" /> AsSpgd()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Shader Particle Geometry</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not a <b>Shader Particle Geometry</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsStat" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Stat" /> AsStat()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Static</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not a <b>Static</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsTxst" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Txst" /> AsTxst()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Texture Set</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not a <b>Texture Set</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsWeap" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Weap" /> AsWeap()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Weapon</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not a <b>Weapon</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <method name="AsWthr" extension="true" gametitle="Skyrim">
    <signature>
      <see cref="Forms.Skyrim.Wthr" /> AsWthr()</signature>
    <summary>
            Converts this form to a <b>Weather</b> form or returns <c>null</c> if this form is not a <b>Weather</b> form.
            </summary>
  </method>
  <remarks>
    <p>
            When a variable refers to an unknown or generic form it means that only the common form properties and methods are available. 
            In order to access all properties of the form the variable must be cast to the specific form using the appropriate extension method.
            </p>
    <p>
            Unknow or generic forms can be retrieved via the <see cref="Helpers.Forms" /> helper method <code>Forms.Find()</code>
            or by iterating a mixed <see cref="Forms.FormCollection" /> such as the collection of forms associated with a <b>Form List</b> form.
            </p>
    <p>
            Unsupported forms are forms that have been loaded but the appliaction does not know anything about such form. 
            Unsupported forms can be assigned to properties of supported forms or added to mixed <see cref="Forms.FormCollection" />.
            Unsupported forms cannot be converted to a specific form.
            </p>
    <p>
            Unresolved forms are threaded the same way unsupported forms are treated, except that their Editor ID is always <c>null</c>.
            Unresolved forms come about from references to forms that do not exist due to an error in a plugin, 
            or because the tool deliberately skipped these forms while loading plugin.
            Saving plugin that reference unresolved forms will produce a warning, but will work as intended as long as the form really exists.
            </p>
  </remarks>
</type>